sibers.com 2009-06-19

# 

## Privacy Policy

We've created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our company's commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

 **Email Information – and take all possible measures**

We at Sibers.com, HireRussians.com and Key-Soft.net are aware of the growing concern of users regarding the widespread distribution of their personal information, and taking measures to protect our customer's and visitor's privacy. We do not sell or redistribute any e-mail addresses to third parties or spammers.

 **Information related to any project development**

The information submitted, whether it is a request for a quote, project description, files describing any project details or simply joining our news list, remains confidential and is for our records only until otherwise agreed. Any project details received via the website are subject for the non disclosure agreement by default. That means we cannot share this with any third party. We may use some non-confidential information about the projects we develop on our site if we have no obligation to keep such information confidential.

 **Links to other resources**

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

 **Confidentiality**

These measures, along with our belief that it is up to the individual to determine who receives and what may be done with their personal information, insure that any information submitted on our site will be kept confidential. Our company is the sole owner of the information provided by you. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

 **How to Contact Us**

If you have other questions or concerns about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, you can contact us at [info@sibers.com](mailto:info@sibers.com), [info@hirerussians.com](mailto:info@hirerussians.com), or via postal mail at Lavrentyeva ave. 6/1 office 605, Novosibirsk, Russia 630090 or call +1 (800) 521-4091.
